{
    "id": "c5849d3c1d8b4a40823080e2917681b1",
    "title": "Infinitives With And Without To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8f023c8cede4f9991dc3019a69df32e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ought …………………. your ways.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mend",
                "to mend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1961756cbdb1456d87af2fb0844d5baf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t ………………. anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "to say"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93e8df24c6ee4f0ab69992c2e07f9343"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was told ………………. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "to leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06e17021454445119655d8dffa68f59a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ………………….. what she wants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "to see"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "69a06dca5f2644e5b1b64d3ccddf9cd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t let my children ………………….. up late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "to stay"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0aadee9145ad42f8a080b68ce86e9d4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t see him ...................... in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "to come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58cd7d88b6af4228a7470b7555aba9d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We both heard her ……………….. that she was leaving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "to say"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2277e26e76dd46f890399f39b1211c14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you feel the earth ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "move",
                "to move"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60917be7fe6841958120895b1f3e2ef0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me ………………… the car?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "load",
                "to load",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7a29143eb7c74b139d2b8b5ff76c9328"
        }
    ]
}